Do you think there's a town
in Missouri or someplace...
미조리인지 어딘지에
'샘플'이란 데가 있는 거야
...called Sample?
And as you're driving into the town,
there's a sign and it says:
그 마을에 들어서면 이런
표지가 있지
"You're in Sample."
'여기는 샘플입니다'
- 안녕
-How did it go with Pete?
-Tell us.
- 피트랑은 어떻게 됐어?
- 얘기 좀 해봐
You're not gonna believe this.
So I go
못 믿을 거야
내가 거길 갔는데...
I'm sorry. Excuse us.
- 미안합니다
- 실례할게요
-It's a little crowded. Do you mind?
-Could you skooch?
자리가 없어서 그런데...
같이 앉으면 안될까요?
좀 땡겨 앉죠
Move over just a little bit.
- 조금만 비켜줘요
- 그래요
- 계속 땡겨요
- 알았어요
IKeep on skooching.
So, guys, listen.
I go over there and, you know, I'm
- 그래서, 내가 말야...
- 그래
Why? What is wrong with me?
- 왜, 난 왜 이 모양이냐구
- 왜 그래?
-What's the matter?
-Tim...
집사람이 산부인과 의사랑
눈이 맞은 것 같아
... I have a feeling...
... my wife is sleeping
with her gynecologist.
How do you know?
어떻게 알았는데?
- 항상 들락거리니까
- 그래
-He's got access.
-I know.
그냥 그런 느낌이
드는 거 있잖아
It's a feeling you get.
Like when you're in
somebody else's bowling shoes?
볼링장에 갔는데 다른 사람
신발을 신고 있는 것처럼?
바로 그거야
That's the one.
-So you went to Pete's.
-What happened?
- 피트한테 가서...
- 어떻게 됐어?
Why is this happening to me?
왜 이런 일이 일어나냐구
상처 때문일지도 모르지
Maybe it's my wound.
Forget it.
관두자
상처가 아직 안 나았어?
It's not healed yet?
고름이 질질 나온단 말야
크림 좀 줄래요? 여기 있네
It's oozing!
Would you pass the cream?
There's the cream.
Thank you very much.
고마워요
Tomas, this is gonna be hard,
but I wanted it to come from me.
토마스, 다른 사람한테 듣기
전에 내가 직접 말해야겠어
-What is it?
-I've been sleeping with your wife.
뭔데?
자네 부인이랑 눈맞은 사람
나야
당신이 산부인과 의사예요?
You're the gynecologist?
이봐요, 사적인 대화를
나누는 중이잖아요
I'm trying to have
a private conversation.
냅킨 좀 줄래요?
냅킨 좀 달라니까요
Can I have a napkin?
Could you please hand me a napkin?
Just give me the thing, all right?
빨리 좀 못 줘요?
됐어, 관둬!
Enough!
넌 내 친구도 아냐
우린 끝났어
And you are no longer my friend!
We are finished! Nada! No more!
이제 우린 남남이야
넌 배신자야
You are a bastard for doing that!
연락하지도 마
Stay away from me!
토마스!
Come back!
모니카, 너 무슨 얘기하던
중이었지?
So what were you gonna tell us?
I have no idea.
까먹었어
The One With the Ultimate Fighting Champion
피트가 무슨 얘길 하려고
했던 거야?
What was the big news
Pete wanted to tell you?
Or should I say, "Mrs. Monica Becker"?
'모니카 베커'가 돼달라고
했니?
그 사람 성 쓰지 마
네 성을 계속 쓰라구
Oh, keep your name.
Don't take his name.
결혼해 달란 게 아니었어
He didn't ask me to marry him.
그러니까 그 사람 성을
쓰면 더 안되지
Then definitely don't take his name!
He wanted to tell me he's going
to compete in some Ultimate...
싸우고 뒹구는 '얼티밋 파이팅'
시합인지 뭔지에 나갈 거래
...Fighting Competition thingy.
-Pete?
-Why? What is it?
- 피트가?
- 그게 뭔데?
I don't know exactly.
It's sort of like wrestling.
나도 모르겠어
레슬링 같은 건가봐
그런 옷 입는 건 아니고
But without the costumes.
And it's not fake.
It's totally brutal.
그거 장난 아냐
얼마나 잔인한데
두 사람이 링에서 싸우는데
규정이 없는 게 규정이야
It's two guys in the ring and
the rules are, "There are no rules"!
You can bite and pull
people's hair and stuff?
물어뜯고 머리카락 잡아당기고
그런단 말야?
Anything goes except eye-gouging
and fish-hooking.
그래, 눈 찌르기랑 낚시질만
빼고 다 할 수 있어
- 낚시질이 뭔데?
- 그게 뭐냐면...
-What's fish-hooking?
-What's fish-hook
Thanks. That would have been
hard to describe.
고맙다, 어떻게 말해야 할지
암담했는데...
What is that taste?
맛이 왜 이래?
내 손 깨끗해
방금 오리 씻겨주고 왔는데
My hands are totally clean.
I just gave the duck a bath.
따뜻하게 맞아줘서 고맙네
같은 팀에서 일하게 돼 기쁘네
Thanks for the warm welcome.
It's good to have you guys on my team.
I come to play. I hope you do too.
다 함께 열심히 뛰어보자구
자, 그럼 나가서 뛰어볼까?
Let's go out there and get them!
And remember:
명심해, 우리 팀에 '나'는
없다는 걸
There is no "I" in "team."
'내'가 있어야 '우리'도 있지
다들 내 사무실로 가자구
Yes, but there's two in "martini."
So, everybody, back to my office.
재밌는 친구, 이름이 뭐지?
You! Chuckles. What's your name?
빙입니다
죄송해요, 전 그냥...
It's Bing, sir.
I'm sorry. I was just....
아니, 자네 얘기 들었어
재밌군, 재밌는 거 좋아
No, no. I heard what you said.
Funny. I like funny.
그럼...
This team's about hard work,
but it's also about having fun.
재밌게 열심히
일하는 거 좋지
Good to have you aboard, Bing!
잘 해보자구, 빙!
그래요, 라이더
위노나 라이더 여섯이요
That's right. Ryder.
Winona Ryder for six.
Thank you.
고마워요
됐어, 예약했어
Yeah. We have the reservations.
- 신난다!
- 잘했어, 친구!
All right, buddy! Way to go!
뭐하는 거야?
Dude, what are you doing?
오늘 내 상사가 아무렇지 않은
얼굴로 내 엉덩일 때리더라구
Thank you. My boss keeps slapping my
butt, and acting like it's no big deal.
What'd you do about it?
그래서 어떻게 했어?
가만있었지
I didn't do anything.
I didn't want to be the guy...
상사가 엉덩이 때리는 걸 물고
늘어지는 사람은 되기 싫었거든
...who has a problem with his boss
slapping his bottom.
그래?
난 그 사람이 부러운데
I gotta tell you, I think it's okay
to be that guy.
그래, 별 거 아냐
Maybe it's that jock thing.
You know, how football players
pat each other after touchdowns.
풋볼 선수들이 터치다운
하고 나서 이러잖아
You know, I don't understand guys.
난 모르겠는데
모니카가 맛있는 스튜 끓였다고
가슴을 만져주거나 하진 않잖아
I mean, I would never congratulate
Monica on a great stew...
... by, you know, grabbing her boob.
진짜 맛있는 스튜를 끓였으면
그 속에 머리만 박아주면 돼
I know. For a really great stew,
you'd just...
...stick your head in between them.
Can we please go eat?
그만하고 먹으러 갈래?
- 뭐 먹을까?
- 스튜만 빼고 아무거나
-Yeah, what are we getting?
-Anything but stew.
So from now on, don't give
your boss a chance to get you.
챈들러, 이제부터 네 상사한테
기회를 주지 마
엉덩이를 돌리지 말라구
Don't turn your back to him.
Or you could teach him
a lesson, you know?
안 그럼 따끔하게
혼내주든가
엉덩이에 고약한 냄새가
나는 걸 발라놓는 거야
What you do is rub something that
smells really bad on your butt, right?
Then, when he goes to smack you,
his hand will smell.
네 엉덩이를 때리면
손에서 냄새가 나는 거지
Now, what could you rub on your butt
that would smell bad?
엉덩이에 뭘 발라야 고약한
냄새가 날까?
쟤가 대통령 되면 어떨까?
What if Joey was President?
- 레이첼, 하나만 물어보자
- 그래
Can I ask you something?
Okay, you can totally say no...
싫으면 싫다고 해
로스한테 여자 소개시켜줘도
괜찮겠니?
...but would it be okay with you
if I set Ross up on a date?
With who?
누구?
내 친구, 보니
My friend Bonnie.
She always thought Ross was cute...
로스가 귀엽다고 항상 그랬거든
나한테 자리 좀 만들어 달래
...and she asked if I could set it up.
네가 싫다면...
-But if that's not cool....
-Which one is Bonnie?
보니가 누구지?
2년 전 내 생일 파티에
왔었잖아
You remember her from
my birthday party?
보통 키에 보통 체격에...
Average height...
... medium build, bald....
머리가 없어
That's fine.
좋아
정말? 잘됐다
Great! Okay! Good for you!
All right!
You are iron! You are steel!
넌 강철이야, 무쇠라구!
Let me ask you, how come when I call
your computer support line...
하나만 물어볼게
컴퓨터 상담하러 전화하면
왜 한 시간 넘게 기다려야 하지?
... I have to wait an hour and a half?
We're adding operators all the time.
Could we concentrate on my training?
오퍼레이터들을 계속 투입하고
있으니까, 훈련에나 신경써요
이메일을 못 받으니까
신경질이 나잖아
It's just hard when I know
I have e-mail I can't get.
- 안녕
- 모니카
Hi, honey.
어서 와
On the table. On the table, please.
엎드려
친구들이 그러는데
자기 하겠다는 시합 말야
So listen, my friends were
telling me a little bit about...
...this Ultimate Fighting thing.
굉장히 위험하다던데
It sounds really dangerous.
I don't want you to get hurt
because I kind of like you.
자기 다치는 거 싫어
자기를 좋아하니까
나도 다치는 거 싫어
걱정마, 잘 할 거야
I don't want to get hurt either.
I'm being smart about this.
See these guys? They're
the best trainers in the world.
이 사람들 보이지?
최고의 트레이너들이야
And Hoshi here used to be
a paid assassin.
여기 호치는 옛날에
해결사였어
화가!
화가였다는 얘기였어
A house painter!
He used to be a house painter!
-Promise me you'll be careful.
-I promise.
- 조심한다고 약속해
- 약속할게
- 우리 오늘 만나는 거지?
- 응
Are we still on for tonight?
Good. Because...
좋아, 그럼...
... maybe we could have
a little workout of our own.
우리만의 시간을
갖는 거야
큰 시합 앞두고
무리하면 안돼
No boom-boom before big fight!
가볍게 끝내자구
How about just a boom?
That was depressing.
I just bought a pretzel...
기분 나빠, '페임'에 나오는
학생한테 훔쳐온 기분이야
...from one of the kids from Fame.
영화보러 갈까?
Ready to go to the movies?
Oh, this is Bonnie!
레이첼, 여긴 보니야
안녕
This is Bonnie?
이게 보니야? 보니?
당신이 보니예요?
This is Bonnie? You're Bonnie?
I can show you an l.D. if you want.
신분증이라도 보여줘요?
아뇨, 전에 봤을 때랑
많이 달라져서요
Oh, no. You look a lot different
than the last time I saw you.
Oh, yeah. Well, I just
started wearing bras again.
네, 브래지어를 다른 걸로
바꿨거든요
Oh, that must be it.
그래서 그런가?
Have fun tonight.
그럼, 재밌게 보내
Thanks. You too.
- 고마워, 너도
- 그래
You said she was bald.
머리가 없댔잖아
She was bald. She's not now.
옛날엔 없었는데
지금은 있네
How could you not tell me
she has hair?
머리가 있다는 말을
왜 안 한 거야?
나 원래 그런 말
잘 안 하잖아
I don't know.
I hardly ever say that about people.
Oh, well this is just perfect!
이게 뭐야!
Well, I'm sorry.
I thought you said it was okay.
미안해
너도 괜찮다고 했잖아
그랬지, 괴상망측한
대머리라고 생각했으니까
I said it was okay when I thought
she was some weird bald chick.
근데 머리털이
부숭부숭하잖아
That girl has got hair
all over her head!
-Maybe Ross won't like her personality.
-Does she have a bad personality?
잘 안될지도 몰라
성격이 맘에 안 들지도 모르지
성격이 영 아니야?
Oh, no, Bonnie's the best!
아니, 좋아
Bing!
빙!
자네 제안서 읽었네
홈런 감이야
Read your CompuTek proposal.
Real home run.
빗나갔잖아
이리 대!
Barely got you that time.
Get over here!
빨리!
Come on.
Oh, yeah! Good one.
좋았어, 아주 좋아
계속 열심히들 하라구
That was a good one.
IKeep at it, team!
왜 저래?
-What is with him?
-"With him"?
무슨 소리야?
자네를 예뻐하니까 그렇지
You're his favorite.
You're his guy!
We never get smacked.
우린 한번도 안 때려
저번에 한번 때렸잖아
That's not true.
He smacked you once.
Not on purpose.
He ricocheted off you and got me.
자네를 때리려다가
빗나가서 내가 맞은 거지
I'm telling you,
I need some smacks.
나도 좀 맞아봤으면 좋겠어
우리 애가 가을에
다머스에 가거든
I got a kid starting Dartmouth.
Dartmouth? Who went to Dartmouth?
Dartmouth sucks!
다머스? 누가 다머스에 가?
다머스는 꽝이야
- 자네가 가나, 빙?
- 아뇨
-You go to Dartmouth?
-No, sir.
There you go!
그래야지!
이거 봐
God, Ross! What is that?
오빠, 이게 뭐야?
'얼티밋 파이팅' 콤보야
The Ultimate Fighting Combo.
I saved 30 cents.
Plus, I get to keep the cup.
30센트 깎아주고
컵도 가져가도 된대, 잘됐지?
뉴욕 출신으로
From New York City, New York...
...appearing in his Ultimate
Fighting Championship debut...
'얼티밋 파이팅'시합 챔피언전에
데뷔하는 선수입니다
막나가는 비즈니스 스타일로
유명하죠
... he's known for his
confrontational business style!
신사숙녀 여러분
소개합니다
Ladies and gentlemen, introducing...
피트 베커!
... Pete Becker!
사랑해, 피트
I love you, Pete!
그에 맞서는 경쟁자는
헌팅턴 비치에서 온
And his opponent,
from Huntington Beach, California...
136킬로그램의 거구입니다
... he's a 300-pound
streetfighter...
...Tank Abbott!
탱크 애보트!
Pete?
피트!
저 사람 덩치 봐
Pete?
-That guy's pretty huge.
-Don't worry.
걱정마, 상대의 힘과 무게를
이용하는 법을 배웠거든
I'll use his strength
and weight against him.
저 사람 이제 큰일났다
Well, then that guy is in serious,
serious trouble.
좋아, 뭉개버려요!
You go get him. Let's go!
좋아요, 시작합니다
준비됐어요?
Here we go, gentlemen.
Are you ready?
Then let's get it on!
준비됐죠? 시작!
자기, 나야
It's me.
모니카
Monica.
자기가 얼마나
자랑스러운지 알아?
Can I just tell you how proud
I am of you?
사람들이 등신이라고 손가락질
하는데 그 말이 먹힐 것 같아?
It would be nice after hearing
20,000 people chant, "You suck!"
처음엔 정신나갔다고
생각했지만, 결국 해냈잖아
I thought you were nuts at first...
... but you did it.
나중에 뒤돌아봤을 때
후회는 없을 거야
Now you can just look back at this
with no regrets.
Look back?
뒤돌아봐?
You're not gonna keep going?
이제 그만하는 거 아냐?
Let me ask you a question:
Am I the Ultimate Fighting Champion?
하나만 물어볼게
내가 챔피언 됐어?
아니, 하지만...
Well, no. But
챔피언이 될 때까지
절대로 멈추지 않을 거야
I'm not gonna stop until I'm
the Ultimate Fighting Champion.
That guy stood on your neck
until you passed out.
그 사람, 자기 기절할 때까지
목에 올라탔잖아
내 얘기 들어봐
Let me tell you a story.
내가 '모스 865'를 하루아침에
만들어낸 줄 알아? 아냐
When I set out to create MOSS 865,
do you think it happened overnight?
No. There was MOSS 1
that burned down my dad's garage.
처음엔 '모스 원'을 만들었는데
차고에서 타 없어져 버렸지
'모스 투'는 1월 계획표로
써 버렸지
There was MOSS 2 that would only
schedule appointments in January.
'모스 862'를 만들면서
배운 게 많아
And 862 others that I learned from.
Just like I learned from this fight,
never to let a guy stand on my neck.
이번 시합에서는 목을 타고
누르면 안된다는 교훈을 배웠지
You didn't know that already?
그건 벌써 알고 있던
거잖아
이제 더 잘 할 수 있어
Look, I'm gonna get better.
Okay? I promise you.
알았지? 약속할게
잘 해야 돼
빨리!
Just get a lot better.
Fast.
그리고, 호치가 그러는데 자기가
링에 나와서 집중이 안된 거래
One other thing.
Hoshi thinks you being ringside
may have affected my concentration.
그래,
그게 문제였나보네
That was the problem.
오빠
피트 시합 얼마나 남았어?
-How long until Pete's fight?
-About five minutes.
5분
지금 상대 선수랑 인터뷰해
They're interviewing his opponent.
Apparently, he trains by going to lran
and pulling the arms off thieves.
이란에 가서 도둑들 팔 뽑는
기술을 익혔대
- 핫도그 먹을래?
- 네 개 줘
-Hot dog?
-Four, please.
떨려 죽겠어
I'm really nervous.
고마워
Thank you.
So how did it go with Bonnie?
로스, 보니랑 어떻게 됐어?
Oh, I gotta tell you,
I wasn't expecting to like her at all.
솔직히...
아무 기대 없이 나갔어
누굴 좋아하게 될 것 같지
않았거든
I actually wasn't expecting
to like anyone right now.
근데... 보니는 맘에 들어
But she's really terrific.
안됐다
It's too bad.
아니, 좋았다니까
No, I'm saying I liked her.
기운 내
세상의 반은 여자니까
There are other fish in the sea.
피비, 좋다니까
우리 또 만나기로 했어
I think she's great, okay?
We're going out again.
I hear you. Are you capable
of talking about anything else?
알아들었어
그 말 밖에 할 말이 없니?
어떤 게 내 터키 버거야?
Which one's my turkey burger?
발 옆에 있는 거, 미안
The one next to my foot.
Sorry.
시합 시작한다
-Fight's starting!
-We'll be right in.
금방 들어갈게
네 상사가 엉덩이 또 때렸어?
So did your boss try
to slap you again today?
Nine times.
아홉 번이나!
로션까지 발랐다니까
I had to put on lotion.
괜찮아, 내일 가서
시험을 해볼 생각이거든
But it'll be okay.
Tomorrow, I conduct an experiment.
And if all goes as planned,
my butt will be smack-free.
계획대로면 내 엉덩이는
접근 금지 구역이 되는 거야
Fight's over!
시합 끝났다
저기요, 덕
Excuse me, Doug?
스포츠 팬, 계세요?
Hey there, sports fan!
Bing! You got those numbers for me?
빙, 자료 뽑아왔나?
No. I didn't do them.
아뇨, 안했어요
깜빡했나?
You forgot?
아뇨, 그냥 안했죠
No, I just didn't do them.
대신 친구들하고 어울려서
맥주 마시고 놀았어요
Instead, I hung out with some
friends and had a couple of beers.
So I certainly don't
deserve praise. Verbal...
전 칭찬받을 자격 없어요
말이든... 행동이든요
...or otherwise.
나도 어제 완전히 망가졌어
I got tanked myself last night.
Pretty dicey drive home.
어떻게 집에 갔는지
눈이 뵈는 게 없더라구
Tappan Zee Bridge never looked smaller.
That's okay. You're still
my number-one guy! Bing!
괜찮아, 그래도 자네는
예쁘기만 해, 빙!
Doug!
덕?
I'm a little bit uncomfortable with
the way that you express yourself.
감정 표현 방법이 저한테는
약간 불편하거든요
말버릇 나쁜 거 말인가?
내가 좀 그렇긴 하지
Is it the swearing?
Is it the constant swearing?
Because I gotta tell you, if it is,
you can just kiss my ass!
그게 정 불편하면...
엿이나 먹으라구!
아뇨, 그것 때문이 아니에요
그것보다는...
It's not about the swearing.
It's more about...
...the way that you occasionally...
뜨거운 열정을 손에
듬뿍 담아서...
...concentrate your enthusiasm...
...on my buttocks.
제 엉덩이를 때리는 거요
오해하지 말구요
절 좋아하시는 건 고마운데...
Don't get me wrong.
I appreciate the sentiment.
It's just that I have a rather
sensitive posterior.
뒤쪽이 좀 예민하거든요
게다가 다른 사원들이
질투를 해서 말예요
And besides, it's making
all the other guys jealous.
알았네, 이런 말하기 쉽지
않았을 텐데
Well, say no more. You know,
it takes guts to bring this up.
- 빙, 잘 알았네
- 좋아요
Bing, you're okay.
Would you rather live in the
shirt pocket of a sweaty giant...
땀투성이 거인 셔츠 주머니에
살래, 아님 은밀한 데서 살래?
...or inside his shower drain?
세상에
Oh, my God.
Look. It's Ross and that girl.
피비, 저기 봐
로스랑 그 여자야
안돼
이것 좀 봐, 개미야!
Look at that! It's a line of ants!
They're working as a team!
- 팀으로 일하나봐
- 피비!
Right. Oh, yeah. It looks
like Ross is breaking up with her.
로스가 저 여자한테
헤어지자고 말하나봐
달래주려는 모양이네
가자
I hope he lets her down easy.
Look at that! They are not
breaking up! Look at them!
피비, 잘 좀 봐
헤어지는 게 아냐, 보라구
You know what that is?
A second date, that's what that is.
너도 알잖아, 지금 두 번째
데이트 중이란 말야
저 여자가 로스 허벅지에
손을 올리고 있어
Look, she just put her hand
on his thigh.
아냐, 별 거 아냐
쟤가 공격적인 성향이 있거든
That's nothing.
She's very sexually aggressive.
Oh, God!
It's your fault. Now he loves her.
He'll marry her. It's all your fault.
피비, 다 네 잘못이야
둘이 결혼하면 네 탓이라구
너도 괜찮다고 했잖아
You said it was okay.
네가 대머리라고 했으니까
You said she was bald!
Was! Was, was, was!
대머리였어, 대머리였다구
보고만 있을 순 없어
두 사람 갈라놓자
We can't let it happen. We have to do
something. We have to break them up.
네가 들어가서
머리를 확 밀어버려
Just go in there and shave her head!
You owe me one bald girl!
대머리 만들어버리란 말야
우선 숨 좀 쉬어봐
Okay, first of all, breathe.
Second of all, I don't get it.
둘째, 난 이해가 안 가는데
Aren't you the one that decided
you didn't want to be with Ross?
로스랑 헤어지기로 한 거
네 결정 아니었니?
그랬지
이젠 친구가 됐는데
친구가 행복한 게 싫어?
Well, isn't he your friend?
Don't you want him to be happy?
아니
So?
그런데?
이렇게 빨리 행복해질 줄은
몰랐단 말야
It's just, you know, I didn't
expect him to be this happy so soon.
-Oh, no.
-What?
- 이런
- 왜?
We killed them all!
개미 다 죽었겠다
It's not as bad as it looks.
It's a precaution.
괜찮아, 그리 심각한 건 아냐
조심하느라고 그래
척추 움직이면 안되거든
I'm not supposed to move my spine.
Please tell me you're stopping now.
제발 그만한다고 말해줘
난 괜찮아, 시켜만 주면
오늘밤이라도 싸울 거야
I'm fine. I'd fight tonight
if they'd let me.
Now, see this circle
I'm marking off here?
여기 이 원 보이지?
내 '공격 구역'이야
This is my Zone of Terror.
You are insane!
You've got to give this up!
미쳤어, 제발 그만둬
챔피언이 될 때까지
계속할 거야
I can't until I'm
the Ultimate Fighter.
I will do it.
The day will come when children will
argue over who will win a fight...
아이들이 나랑 수퍼맨이 싸우면
누가 이길까 다투는 날이 오겠지
...me or Superman.
수퍼맨을 이긴단 얘긴 아니지만
애들은 순진하잖아
Not that I could beat Superman,
but kids are stupid.
좋아, 앉아서 내 얘기 좀
들어봐
Just sit down.
Please listen to me.
자기는 소질이 없어
챔피언이 될 수가 없다구
You are terrible at this, okay? You
are the worst Ultimate Fighter ever.
절대!
Ever!
척추도 심하게 다치고
I have a torn rotator cuff, a hairline
fracture in my right forearm...
팔도 부러지고 목도 다쳐서
아파 죽겠지만
...and a severely bruised Adam's
apple, but that really hurt.
자기 말이 더 아파
그래서 말인데...
Well, then, you know what?
난 자기 몸 막 굴리는 거
보고 있을 수가 없어
I care about you too much to watch you
hurt yourself like this.
So if you have to do this,
you'll have to do it without me.
꼭 이걸 하겠다면
나 없이 해야 할 거야
If you're asking me to quit...
이걸 그만두라는 건, 나더러
다른 사람이 되라는 얘기야
...then you're asking me
to be someone I'm not.
꼭 해야겠어
I've got to do this.
그럼 난 갈게
Then I've gotta go.
Bye.
- 모니카?
- 응?
Could you leave a note?
I'm on painkillers...
쪽지라도 남겨줄래? 진통제
때문에 내일 기억 못할 것 같아
...and I might not
remember this tomorrow.
So, in conclusion, the lines
all go up, so I'm happy.
결과적으로 상향선이야
그래서 기분 캡이야
다들 잘했어
내일 8시 반에 보자구
Great job, team!
Tomorrow at 8:30.
필, 잘했어
스티븐스, 아주 잘하고 있어
Phil, nice job! Stevens, way to go!
골드버그, 미친 자식
사랑해
Goldberg, you maniac!
I love you!
빙, 잘했어
자네 없인 못 했을 거야
-Couldn't have done it without you.
-Thank you, sir.
감사합니다
Oh, excuse me.
깜빡하고 가방을
두고 왔네요
I forgot my briefcase, you know,
by accident.
- 실수로...
- 그랬겠지
Of course, you did. Forgot
something else too, you bastard!
맨날 깜빡하잖아
멍청하게!
Well, what about you?
자넨 어때?
자네도 뭘 두고 갈 건가?
You're not feeling left out, are you?
아뇨, 아닙니다
속보이잖아요
No, not at all. That's ridiculous.
다들 한 대씩 맞으니까
자네도 맞고 싶지?
Everybody else got one,
and you want one too. Don't you?
그래요
Yes, I do.
좋았어, 친구!
Now, get on out of here, you!
Pete Becker circles the ring.
피트 베커 선수, 빙빙 돌면서
기회를 엿보고 있습니다
Looks like he's just trying
to feel him out.
브루저 선수, 덤빕니다
Bruiser is charging!
도망가, 살고 싶으면 도망가
미친놈아
Run, you crazy, rich freak!
I can't watch this.
못 보겠다
이것 좀 봐
피트가 이기고 있어
Check it out! Pete's winning!
Really?
- 정말?
- 아니!
Bruiser has Becker on the canvas
and is going for his favorite area!
브루저 선수, 베커 선수를
특유의 기술로 후리고 있습니다
저게 특유의 기술이야?
너무 못됐다
Wait! If that's his favorite area,
why is he being so mean to it?
정말 웃긴다
This is ironic.
전에 사귄 리차드는
아이 낳기를 싫어했는데
Your last boyfriend, Richard,
didn't want to have kids.
피트는 낳고 싶어도
못 낳게 됐어
And from the looks of it,
now Pete can't.